{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "React Quiz",
      "isShared": true,
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "front": "Pure Component",
          "back": "a function that does not change any objects or variables that existed before it was called and secondly, it should always return the same result"
        },
        {
          "front": "Impure Component",
          "back": "is a function that changes any objects or variables that existed before rendering and returns an unpredictable result."
        },
        {
          "front": "React Context",
          "back": "is a method or tool gives us a way to share global data across components, especially components in deeply nested hierarchies"
        },
        {
          "front": "Lifting State",
          "back": "to decide which component to create our state variable in, we need to locate the closest common parent."
        },
        {
          "front": "Props",
          "back": "information that every parent component can pass to its child components by passing any JavaScript value through them, including objects, arrays, and functions. "
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "username": "user1",
      "password": "password1",
      "decks": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "name": "User 2 Deck",
          "flashcards": [
            {
              "front": "user2flashcard",
              "back": "user 2 answer"
            },
            {
              "front": "term 2",
              "back": "def 2"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "username": "user2",
      "password": "password2",
      "decks": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "name": "User 2 Deck",
          "flashcards": [
            {
              "front": "user2flashcard",
              "back": "user 2 answer"
            },
            {
              "front": "term 2",
              "back": "def 2"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "username": "Jam3ster",
      "password": "karkari",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "username": "Jam3ster",
      "password": "karkari",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "username": "Jam3ster",
      "password": "karkari",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "username": "user1",
      "password": "password1",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "username": "Jam3ster",
      "password": "karkari",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "username": "Jam3ster",
      "password": "karkari",
      "decks": [],
      "id": 8
    }
  ],
  "userdecks": [
    {
      "user": 1,
      "name": "My Card Deck",
      "id": 1,
      "isShared": false,
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "front": "user2flashcard",
          "back": "user 2 answer"
        },
        {
          "front": "term 2",
          "back": "def 2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "user": 2,
      "name": "My Card Deck",
      "isShared": false,
      "id": 2,
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "front": "user2flashcard",
          "back": "user 2 answer"
        },
        {
          "front": "term 2",
          "back": "def 2"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Test",
      "user": 1,
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "front": "Test",
          "back": "Test"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Test",
      "user": 1,
      "flashcards": [
        {
          "front": "TEst",
          "back": "TEst"
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    }
  ]
}